https://leskincaid.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
"Food/Wine/Entertainment"
Privacy Policy
We at Les Kincaid Enterprises are committed to respecting your privacy. We recognize the need for appropriate protection of personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified, including name, address, e-mail address, or credit card information). The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of what personally identifiable information or personal information we may collect from you when you visit our websites, and how we use such information. This policy applies only to users accessing our websites from the United States. To protect your privacy, we have adopted the following principles, and assure you that we take reasonable steps to see that it is followed within our company:
Information About You
There are times when we may collect personal information from you. For example, when you register with leskincaid.com, Les Kincaid’s Lifestyles electronic newsletters, product giveaways, surveys, or other services, personal information is requested. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most parts of our website, but you may be unable to access certain content, offers, and services.
Use of Information About You
Your e-mail address is added to our electronic mailing list so that, from time to time, we can send you our newsletter or other information and special promotions from Les Kincaid Enterprises. Registrants have the opportunity to opt-out of any third party communications at the time that they register. E-mail addresses submitted to Les Kincaid Enterprises are not shared with third parties.
Accuracy
We do our best to maintain the accuracy of the personal information you supply to us.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All orders are communicated to us via a secure server.
Contacting Les Kincaid Enterprises
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please contact:
Les Kincaid Enterprises
6633 Shelter Lane
Las Vegas, NV 89103-4360
(702) 871-5145
Commitment
We are committed to privacy, and we are actively involved in and support current industry initiatives to preserve individual privacy rights on the Internet. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at les@leskincaid.com. We will address any issue to the best of our abilities.
Email Sign-Up
Join our email list to keep update on our weekly happenings.
Translate
Select LanguageAfrikaansAlbanianAmharicArabicArmenianAzerbaijaniBasqueBelarusianBengaliBosnianBulgarianCatalanCebuanoChichewaChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CorsicanCroatianCzechDanishDutchEnglishEsperantoEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchFrisianGalicianGeorgianGermanGreekGujaratiHaitian CreoleHausaHawaiianHebrewHindiHmongHungarianIcelandicIgboIndonesianIrishItalianJapaneseJavaneseKannadaKazakhKhmerKoreanKurdish (Kurmanji)KyrgyzLaoLatinLatvianLithuanianLuxembourgishMacedonianMalagasyMalayMalayalamMalteseMaoriMarathiMongolianMyanmar (Burmese)NepaliNorwegianPashtoPersianPortuguesePunjabiRomanianRussianSamoanScottish GaelicSerbianSesothoShonaSindhiSinhalaSlovakSlovenianSomaliSpanishSudaneseSwahiliSwedishTajikTamilTeluguThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduUzbekVietnameseWelshXhosaYiddishYorubaZulu
Search
Recent Posts
Find Your Escape
Tangy Barbecue Wings
Spicy Honey Sriracha Dip
Recent CommentsArchives
February 2020
January 2020
Built using Kale Pro by LyraThemes.
